// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the name of the Indian space agency?",
    answer: "ISRO",
    options: ["NASA", "Roscosmos", "JAXA", "ISRO"]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the male gamet cell known as?",
  answer: "Sperm ",
    options: ["Zygot", "Egg ", "Embro", "Sperm "]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the female gamet cell known as?",
    answer: "Egg ",
    options: ["Zygot", "Sperm", "Embro", "Egg "]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "How many life process does a human have?",
    answer: "7",
    options: ["6", "3", "8", "7"]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "How many groups are there in a periodic table?",
    answer: "18",
    options: ["15", "17", "8", "18"]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "How many jouls in one kilojouls?",
    answer: "1000",
    options: ["1500", "500", "250","1000"]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Who was the first person to step on moon?",
    answer: "Neil Armstrong",
    options: ["Michael Collins", "Buzz Aldrin ", "Alan shepard","Neil Armstrong"]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Approximately how old is the Universe?",
    answer: "13.8 billion years",
    options: ["1.7 billion years", "16.9 billion years", "100 million years","13.8 billion years"]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which instrument is used to measure voltage?",
    answer: "Voltmeter",
    options: ["Ammeter", "Resistor", "Cell", "Voltmeter"]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "At what time of day a plant has the most starch?",
    answer: "Night",
    options: ["Night", "Mid day", "All the time","Day"]
  }
];